flowtown.com 2012-03-08

# Creating consumer demand for small business|Demandforce

### Privacy policy 

Demandforce is a leading provider of automatic email-based customer relationship management solutions for automotive repair facilities and dental practices. Leveraging the industry's best email acquisition and management technology, Demandforce's on-demand solution automates customer communications through strategically timed and targeted emails that increases customer satisfaction and loyalty. Demandforce partners with repair facilities and dental practices to expand relationships with customers and build more profitable businesses.

Demandforce is committed to protecting your privacy rights. This page is a summary of Demandforce's Privacy policy. It is not intended to modify or amend our full privacy policy, which Demandforce encourages you to review.

Demandforce's business is built on establishing trust with both our subscribers and their consumers. That trust is essential to our success. In order to establish trust with our subscribers and their consumers as well as visitors to our corporate website, we intend to communicate openly and directly with each and every Demandforce user whenever possible.

We treat our users' information as if it were our own personal information.

Demandforce does not sell, share or rent our users' personally identifiable information unless required by law.

Demandforce does not send any e-mail or other communications without user permission.

Demandforce does not send spam.

Once Demandforce has established trust with our users, we will protect that trust. We stand committed to its protection by being vigilant and constantly improving our service.

#### Demandforce is committed to your privacy

Demandforce is committed to your right to privacy. As a visitor to our website, a Demandforce subscriber or a customer of a Demandforce subscriber ("consumer"), you have the right to control how you or your customers' personal information is used. We provide this Privacy policy so that anyone visiting or using our website is aware of our information gathering and dissemination practices.

#### Summary

The Demandforce Privacy policy affects three groups of users: visitors to our corporate website, Demandforce subscribers and the customers of Demandforce subscribers or consumers. This is a summary of how our privacy policy affects each group of users. For more information, please read the full privacy policy.

##### Consumers

As a customer of a Demandforce subscriber, you are receiving valuable and timely communication, including reminders and "Thank You" notes from a company you have an existing business relationship. You have the right at any time to opt-out from receiving these communications. If you would like to opt-out from receiving these communications please e-mail [privacy@Demandforce.com](mailto:privacy@Demandforce.com). You acknowledge that if you transmit personal health information you waive any right to the privacy of such information.

##### Demandforce subscribers

Demandforce asks new subscribers to provide their name, business name, address, phone and fax numbers and e-mail address as well as a credit card or bank account number. This information is used for customer service and recurring monthly billing purposes only. In order to use Demandforce's service, we upload consumers' personally identifiable information into our secure servers. The collection of our subscribers' information and consumer information is done solely to provide our services to subscribers in accordance with our Subscriber Agreement and Terms of Use. Demandforce will never sell, share or rent the information collected with any third parties unless required by law.

##### Corporate website visitors

Demandforce collects personal information based on requests from visitors to receive further information about our services. Demandforce will never sell, share or rent that information to third parties. If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should contact Demandforce's privacy officer by e-mail at [privacy@Demandforce.com](mailto:privacy@Demandforce.com).

#### How Demandforce collects personally identifiable information

Demandforce collects personal information from users at several different points within our website and hosted product. This enables Demandforce to provide users with better information about our services. Providing your information to Demandforce ensures that a visit to our site or hosted service is simple, convenient and productive. Demandforce will NEVER sell, share or rent your information to others in ways that differ from what is disclosed in this statement.

##### Corporate website

On the corporate website, Demandforce collects information about prospective subscribers and other visitors based on their request to receive further information about our services. A visitor to our site will be asked to provide contact information such as name, business name, address, phone and fax numbers and e-mail address. We use this information only to contact the visitor about the services for which they have requested further information.

##### Hosted product

Demandforce asks new subscribers to provide their name, business name, address, phone and fax numbers and e-mail address. We call this "Subscriber Information". As a new subscriber, you will also be asked to provide payment information such as a credit card or bank account number, which is used for monthly billing purposes only. As part of Demandforce's service deployment process, we securely upload your customers' personally identifiable information (we call this "Consumer Information") into our secure servers. This process is performed so Demandforce can provide our services to consumers on your behalf. The collection of Subscriber Information and Consumer Information is done solely to provide our services to you in accordance with your Subscriber Agreement and Terms of Use.

##### Log files

As is true of most websites, Demandforce gathers certain information automatically and stores it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser types, page views, referring URL and a date/time stamp.

##### Cookies

A cookie is a small text file containing a unique identification number that is transferred from a web server to the end user's hard disk, enabling the serving party to track the website activities of the user. Demandforce uses cookies to help personalize your experience with our website and to ensure that no unauthorized users can access our subscribers' web pages within our service. We do not issue any cookies which enable third parties to track the activities of end users.

#### How Demandforce protects personally identifiable information

##### Your personally identifiable information

Demandforce will not sell, share or rent personally identifiable information, except as may be required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or other legal process.

##### Consumer information

Demandforce will not use Consumer Information for the purposes of directly marketing to, or otherwise communicating directly with those consumers about Demandforce or any third party products or services.

#### How Demandforce may use the information we collect

Demandforce does collect and aggregate broad demographic information that we may use in different ways:

  * Demandforce may sell or share with our partners and advertisers aggregated demographic information compiled from Subscriber Information and/or Consumer Information. This information will not link aggregate user data with personally identifiable information or otherwise make it available.
  * Demandforce may use this information to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track user's movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. This information may also be used for the purpose of monitoring and tracking use of our hosted site in order to improve product delivery to our subscribers.

#### Choice and Opt-Out

Demandforce always provides the ability for users of our website and hosted product to opt-out of having personally identifiable information used as part of our service offering. All e-mails Demandforce sends out on behalf of our subscribers to provide an immediate opt-out mechanism. In addition, any visitor to our site, subscriber to our service or consumer may e-mail us at [privacy@Demandforce.com](mailto:privacy@Demandforce.com) to opt-out of receiving any further correspondence from us.

#### The CAN SPAM act of 2003

The e-mails Demandforce sends on behalf of our subscribers do not constitute spam. Demandforce is in full compliance with the CAN SPAM Act of 2003. 

#### Links to other sites

This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Demandforce is not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. When you leave our site, we encourage you to read the privacy statements of each and every website that you visit to review their use of personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected at Demandforce's website and its hosted service.

#### Updating personally identifiable information

Subscribers to our service may update their personal information or their customers' personal information at will by logging into their home page on our hosted product site. Our software is configured to synchronize Consumer Information on a regular basis with the related subscriber's consumer database, so any updates, changes or opt-out requests communicated directly to our subscribers by their consumers will be automatically uploaded into our site, keeping our site up-to-date with current and correct Consumer Information.

#### Security

Demandforce takes the highest precautions to protect our subscribers' information. When you submit sensitive information via the corporate website or our hosted product, your information is protected both online and offline using standard security best practices such as firewalls, encryption and intrusion detection. Full backups are performed every week on the entire file system and incremental backups are done daily. Finally, all hosted servers are kept physically secure in world-class data centers.

#### Changes to this privacy policy

Demandforce will update this policy from time to time. A "last revised" date will always be included at the top of the statement. To keep up-to-date with Demandforce's privacy policy, please check this page periodically.

#### Contact information

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or if you feel that Demandforce is not abiding by its posted privacy policy, you can contact us by e-mailing your questions or concerns to [privacy@Demandforce.com](mailto:privacy@Demandforce.com) or mail us at 22 Fourth Street, 12th Floor, San Francisco, CA 94104.
